Shubham Mahalkar

Android Mobile App Developer

N7, G1 (210), Triveni Nagar, Cidco, Aurangabad, Maharashtra +91 8087163177 smahalkar@gmail.com

PROFILE SUMMARY

Well experienced Android Mobile Application Developer is aiming to acquire a challenging career with a solid company utilizing the opportunity to offer proven and developing skills within the company.

Mobile application development with 1+ years of proven experience in Android App Development and Project Execution.

EXPERIENCE

Aug 2020 – Present

Coding Visions Infotech Pvt. Ltd.

July 2019 - Aug 2020

Android Developer, Alpha Developer Team Solutions LLP.

PROJECTS

Spardha Vahini

This app has been developed for preparation of MPSC and other state level exam. It provides information about current affairs, quizzes for different exams, and provides way for applying job links.

Tea Club

This app has been developed for cafe Tea Club. After scanning QR code located on table is app will show the menu and will allow user to order.

Go Cart - Ecommerce App

This one is a shopping and ecommerce platform where the products are sorted category wise and displayed along with their prices. The user can add to cart the required items and request delivery.

Go for Event - Event Management App

This app allows you search for lawns or function halls around, check their availability and book them from the comfort of your home for Events such as weddings, sports, corporate meetings, festivities, birthdays, etc.

SVACON - Event Management App

This app manages Doctors' conferences and their activities with the help of QR codes uniquely assigned to each attendant doctor. <u>Play Store</u>

Open Network

Open network is a social media app where registered users can have a one to one chat with each other. They can also update and delete posts, like and comment on others' posts. One key feature of this app is that it allows you to set timer for the duration that you want the post to be active for.

OPD App

With 3 modules, viz. Doctor, patient and receptionist, this app manages the appointment and other clinic activities.

CORE SKILLS

Android App Development

UI Design

GitHub

Android Studio

Java

Kotlin

ANDROID SPECIFIC SKILLS

Activities, Services, Broadcasts

Fragments & Material Design REST API Integration (Volley, Retrofit)

Google Maps

MySQL, SQLite

Social Media Integration

OTHER TECH STACK

PHP Web services

Adobe XD, Figma

XAMPP

Windows, Linux

SOFT SKILLS

Communication

Problem Solving

HOBBIES

Listing to Music

Mobile Games

Octo Beer Fest

This app was developed for a beer fest that was to be held in Aurangabad. It manages all activities right from user registration to their choice of brands, with the help of unique QR codes of each user. Play Store

MP Science Academy

This is a student attendance app which uses QR codes to mark the attendance of every student. There is also a parent's module for parents to keep a check on their child's activities and progress.

KONTO – Contact sharing App

Konto eases the process of sharing and saving contacts in your android phones. It allows you to categorize contacts and also store information other than contact numbers.

PERSONAL APPS ON GOOGLE PLAY STORE

Source Codes: Android App Development Tutorials

Source Codes app showcases Animation source codes, Custom UI source codes, GitHub source codes, Material color codes, Material design components and Video tutorials. This app is designed for android developers, it contains references and open-source projects. Play Store

Android eBooks for Java and Kotlin

Android eBooks provides a platform to learn android coding with coding eBooks. Play Store

EDUCATION

2016 - 2019

MCA from BAM University, MGM's JNE College, Aurangabad.

April 2016

BCS from BAM University, Indraraj College, Sillod.

68.13%

Feb 2013

HSC (Science) at Shiv Chhatrapati College, Aurangabad.

47.17%

March 2011

SSC Dharmaveer Sambhaji Vidyalay, Aurangabad.

61.60%

LANGUAGES

Marathi

Hindi

English

ALL PROJECTS HERE mahalkarshubham.github.io

OR SCAN







